Guide to the Alexander Sprunt and Son Records, 1779-1960 RL.10194
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Alexander Sprunt and Son records
1779-1960
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Alexander Sprunt & Son (Wilmington, N.C.)
RL.10194
6082 items
Cotton firm from Wilmington, N.C., that for a short period was probably the largest cotton exporting house in the United States. Collection includes account books, ledgers, journals, cashbooks, purchase and sales journals, inventories, other subsidiary books, and some office files and correspondence. Goods were purchased from the Carolinas, Georgia, Texas, and other states and processed in the firm's compress facilities and sold to Great Britain, France, Germany, and elsewhere in Europe.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Historical note
Alexander Sprunt & Son, Inc., cotton exporters, was established in 1866 by Alexander Sprunt (1815-1884), an immigrant from Scotland. He was associated with and succeeded by his sons, James Sprunt (1847-1924), and William H. Sprunt, the former being the senior partner of the business. During part of the company's history, it was the largest exporter of cotton in the country. It had a significant effect upon the structure of the cotton market and upon the growth of Wilmington as a port. Before 1881 that city was not regarded as a cotton port, but thirty years later it was one of the most important ports in the country. In 1907 alone Sprunt shipped 501,000 bales, operated six compresses, and employed 1000 workers.
The company drew its business chiefly from Georgia and the Carolinas. Before 1875 the movement of the crop depended upon factors, or agents of teh planters at convenient ports, port buyers, and the receivers in the North who sold it to domestic and foreign mills. In 1879 Sprunt pioneered teh practice, later adopted at other Southern ports, of the direct employment of transatlantic steamers which eventually eliminated the middlemen and their commissions. By 1908, more than fifty steamers were being chartered annually by the company which eight years later purchased The City of Wilmington, the first transatlantic steamer owned by an individual or corporation in North Carolina.
Sprunt relied upon the compress operation for his profit, rather than upon a margin in the price of cotton. The farmer received the Liverpool or continental market price, less the cost of transportation only. The compresses were primarily the facilities of the Champion Compress and Warehouse Company and also teh Wilmington Compress and Warehouse Company. The Ship Channel Compress Company of Houston, Texas, was part of the firm's expansion outside of the Southern Atlantic states. Branch offices functioned at various times in New York City, Boston, Savannah, Memphis, Charlotte, and elsewhere. Numerous offices and agencies were maintained in Europe, such as those at Liverpool, Bremen, Le Havre, and Rotterdam. The firm operated in Wilmington until the 1950s when it was moved to Memphis, Tennessee.
There were various changes in the partnership agreements and in the later corporate structure of the business, many of which are recorded in the minutes or in the office files described in this inventory. Sprunt and Hinson was the initial firm. It was dissolved and replaced by Alexander Sprunt and Son in 1875. The partnership gave way to a corporation in 1919 with the chartering of Alexander Sprunt and Son, Inc., which remained its basic form. The Sprunt Corporation, a holding company, was established in 1931 in Delaware for tax purposes; its name was changed in 1937 to Alexander Sprunt and Son, Inc.
For more information, see: Killick, J.R. "The Transformation of Cotton Marketing in the Late Nineteenth Century: Alexander Sprunt and Son of Wilmington, N.C., 1884-1956." The Business History Review Vol. 55, No. 2 (Summer, 1981): 143-169.
Provenance
The Alexander Sprunt and Son Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 1969.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of an extensive, but incomplete, set of account books, remnants of the office file and James Sprunt's correspondence (personal as well as business letters and papers), and pictures. Among the account books there are long series of ledgers, journals, cashbooks, purchase books, and stock inventories that document the company's operations between the 1870s and 1950s. The ledgers date between 1889 and 1952, and there are private ledgers for 1907 through 1931. The volume of minutes covers 1919-1930, but there are a few others among the offices files along with financial statements, 1885-1915, important legal documents of the partnership and corporation, and assorted other papers.
Correspondence and other papers of James Sprunt and the company date between 1884 and 1952, but they are numerous only for 1904, 1906, 1909-1910, and 1919-1921. The letters date mostly to 1904-1910, and 1919-1921, and are largely files of James Sprunt, reflecting his activities in business and interests in secular and theological education, the Presbyterian church in the U.S., and North Carolina history. Notable correspondents and subjects are Alexander Sprunt (1815-1884), Alexander Sprunt (1852-1937), Alexander Sprunt (b. 1898), James Sprunt (1847-1924), Kenneth Mackenzie Murchison, Francis Herman Packer, John Miller Wells, John Campbell White, Edward Jenner Wood, The Laymen's Missionary Movement, and the Presbyterian mission at Kiangyin, China. Account books, minutes, and correspondence are available also for a number of domestic and foreign subsidaries and branch offices, but these are often quite fragmentary. More than thirty pictures, mostly photographs, illustrate the firm's staff, workers, physical plant, and employees as well as other scenes.
Also included are some papers representing various domestic and foreign subsidiaries and branch offices, especially Champion Compress and Warehouse Company, the Wilmington Compress and Warehouse Company, Alexander Sprunt & Son (of Delaware, a holding company), and the company's offices in New York City and Le Havre, France.
Information about the company's history can be found in: James Sprunt's letters of Nov. 6, 1908; Apr. 9, 1909; Jun. 7 and Oct. 22, 1919; an article in Wilmington's Morning Star from Feb. 11, 1921; and Dictionary of American Biography.
Separated Materials
Several collections were acquired with the Alexander Sprunt and Son Records but were separated for individual cataloging. 1. Great Britain Vice Consulate Papers. Wilmington, N.C. 2. N.C. Board of Commissioners of Navigation and Pilotage for the Cape Fear River and Bar Records. 3. Seamen's Friend Society of Wilmington Records. 4. Universal Oil and Fertilizer Co. Records. 5. Thomas F. Wood, Inc. Records. 6. David Gaston Worth Papers. 7. William E. Worth and Co. Records.
Cotton manufacture -- United States; Wilmington (N.C.) -- History; United States -- Commerce -- Germany; United States -- Commerce -- France; United States -- Commerce -- Great Britain; North Carolina -- Economic conditions; Champion (N.C.) -- History; Sprunt, Alexander; Sprunt, Alexander; Presbyterian Church; Packer, Francis Herman; Murchison, Kenneth Mackenzie; Laymen's Missionary Movement (Wilmington, N.C.); Champion Compress and Warehouse Company (Champion, N.C.); Alexander Sprunt & Son (Wilmington, N.C.); Wood, Edward Jenner; Wilmington Compress and Warehouse Company (Wilmington, N.C.); White, John Campbell; Wells, John Miller; Sprunt, James
- Correspondence and Other Papers, 1818-1952 and undated
  Scope and Contents
  James Sprunt had very extensive correspondence files, of which only a small portion has survived. A year's letters were subdivided alphabetically and included both the incoming originals and the outgoing copies. The years represented by a sizeable body of papers are 1904, 1906, 1909-1910, and 1919-1921, but they are probably quite incomplete. All of the papers have been arranged chronologically. The series also contains "other papers," which cannot be identified with their original files. Most of the material came from James Sprunt's files.
  The series represents a variety of Sprunt's personal and professional interests. Business operations, the cotton market, and domestic and foreign economic conditions are constant concerns. There was frequent communication between Sprunt and his relatives and business associates in Liverpool. His work as vice consul for Great Britain and Germany appears occasionally. Prominent among his activities and charities is the Presbyterian Church in the U.S., the southern body of the Presbyterians. He was a member of the First Presbyterian Church and assisted other congregations in Wilmington and Chapel Hill, where he financed the remodeling of the church as designed by architect Hobart Upjohn. He made substantial contributions to the mission in Kiangyin, China. The interdenominational Laymen's Missionary Movement and its general secretary, John Campbell White, are also prominent in the papers, along with the southern Presbyterian part of of that organization. Sprunt was a principle mover in the arrangements for a statue of George Davis, Confederate attorney general and native son of Wilmington, and there is much correspondence about it, including that with Francis Herman Packer, the sculptor. Sprunt was a trustee of the University of North Carolina and a benefactor of Davidson College, and there are communications between him and the schools' students and officials. Other educational institutions represented include Columbia Theological Seminary, Union Theological Seminary, the antecedents of North Carolina Central University, and other colleges and academies in the South, including several historically black colleges. River and harbor improvements at Wilmington are noted. Scattered political correspondence includes references to state elections, the N.C. Supreme Ct., and the U.S. District Court for Eastern N.C., and the Wilmington riots of 1898. There are several letters about the N.C. Literary and Historical Association and the N.C. Folklore Society, and about other episodes of state history, such as blockade running during the Civil War, President Taft's visit to Wilmington in 1909, Governor Benjamin Smith, and the monument for the Revolutionary battle at Moore's Creek. Correspondence with and about Woodrow Wilson mainly concerned a Carnegie pension for Henry Elliot Shepherd, an educator, but there are a few minor items of a political nature. Sprunt communicated with Senators Lee Slater Overman and Furnifold Simmons about various matters.
  Several close relatives of James Sprunt had distinguished careers and are also represented by letters and references: his brother Alexander Sprunt (1852-1937), a Presbyterian clergyman at Charleston, S.C.; Kenneth Mackenzie Murchison, an architect in New York who was a brother-in-law; Edward Jenner Wood, a nephew and physician who was a pioneer in the campaign against pellagra; and Joseph Austin Holmes, another brother-in-law who was a geologist, chief of the technological branch of the U.S. Geological Survey in charge of the investigation of mine accidents, 1904-1907, and the first director of the Bureau of Mines established in 1910.
  - Information folder, undated (Box 1)
  - 1818-1904 (Box 1)
  - 1905-1909 Jan. (Box 2)
  - 1909 Feb.-Sept. (Box 3)
  - 1909 Oct.-1910 Jan. (Box 4)
  - 1910 Feb.-1919 Mar. (Box 5)
  - 1919 Mar.-1920 Apr. (Box 6)
  - 1920 Apr.-1921 Feb. (Box 7)
  - 1921 Mar.-Dec. (Box 8)
  - 1922-1952 and undated (Box 9)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 9)
- Office Files, 1914-1917 (Box 9)
  Includes incomplete assorted files from the operations of Sprunt and Son and its firms, such as Champion Compress and Warehouse Company.
  - 1456: Original letters from Frederick Huth and Co., showing basis of extra charge of 2 percent and collection of deposit in Deutsche Nationalbank and Sprun vs. Direction der Disconte Gesellschaft and London and Liverpool Bank of Commerce, 1914-1927 (Box 9)
  - 5410: Chapman-Alexander Tabernacle, 1916-1917 (Box 9)
  - 5472: Wilmington Terminal Warehouse Co., 1930 (Box 10)
  - 6000: Private Letterpress Book, 1893-1900 (Box 10)
    Especially correspondence with Messrs. Laird and Gray of New York. Page 9 documents the purchase by the Sprunts of the Champion Compress and Warehouse Company's entire capital stock.
  - 6001-6002: Hyde Park. Copies of deeds, wills, and other papers on property around Lake Phelps, N.C., 1779-1900s (Box 10)
  - 6003: First National Bank of Wilmington, N.C. Stock certificate, 1892 (Box 10)
  - 6004: The Caledonia Pottery Company. Charter, 1891 (Box 11)
  - 6005: Deed to the library of W.S. Hancock at Wilmington, 1895 (Box 11)
  - 6010: Champion Compress and Warehouse Co. inventories and documents on fire losses, 1899 and 1917 (Box 11)
  - 6023: Champion Compress and Warehouse Co. charters and related papers, 1878-1923 (Box 11)
  - 6028: Alexander Sprunt and Son. Financial statement, 1914-1915 (Box 11)
  - 6030: First National Bank of Wilmington, N.C. Stock and papers on suspension of the bank and subsequent lawsuit, 1877-1895 (Box 11)
  - 6051: Private letter file, 1904-1905 (Box 11)
    Especially correspondence with Liverpool agent.
  - 6078: Partnership agreements, 1884-1916 (Box 11)
  - 6080: Torrey Meeting Account; St. Andrew's Presbyterian Church minutes of congregational meetings; St. Andrew's and First Presbyterian churches, statistics, etc., 1902-1909, 1920 (Box 11)
  - 6083: W.H. Sprunt notebook, 1887, on businessmen in N.C. and S.C.; Cotton receipts, 1889-1890; Voters in the 2nd Ward, 1899; Speech: "Sprunt Monopoly in Control of the Port of Wilmington;" Military Draft, 1918; Summons: American Syndicate of New Jersey vs. James Sprunt et al., 1916; Purchase of Camino (ship), 1916, 1887-1918 (Box 11)
  - 6110: Liverpool partnership agreement, 1911 (Box 11)
  - 6116: Annual statements, 1885-1914 (Box 11)
  - 6135: Mortgage: Murdock Black to James Sprunt, 1881 (Box 12)
  - 6138: Old Papers of Alexander Sprunt, 1867-1878 (Box 12)
  - 6143: Political correspondence preceding Wilmington Riot of 1898 (Box 12)
  - 6144: Partnership certificates, 1908 (Box 12)
  - 6159: Announcements of death of James Sprunt, 1924 (Box 12)
  - 6243: Letters on change of Alexander Sprunt and Son to a chartered corporation, 1919 (Box 12)
  - 6246: Corporation charter and amendments, 1919-1930 (Box 12)
  - 6327: Notes and correspondence from trip to Europe by Alexander and W.H. Sprunt, 1922 May-July (Box 12)
    Trip included France, Belgium, Holland, Germany, Austria, and Italy.
  - 6386: Alexander Sprunt's naturalization papers, undated (Box 12)
  - 6410: Church of the Covenant: chimes donated by the Sprunts, 1923-1924 (Box 12)
  - 6545: The Sprunt Corporation (Delaware): minutes of meetings of stockholders and of board of directors, and related papers, 1931-1937 (Box 12)
  - 6901: Partnership discussion, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Box 13)
  - 7184: Houston Branch blueprints of improvements, 1931-1938 (Box 12, Box 13)
  - 7306: Champion Compress and Warehouse Co.: Stock certificates, 1891-1899 (Box 13)
  - 7318: Correspondence at outbreak of World War I, 1914 Jun.-Oct. (Box 13)
  - 7319: Houston property, 1912 (Box 13)
  - 7320: S.S. City of Savannah, undated (Box 13)
  - 7321: Various deeds, 1833-1873 (Box 13)
  - 7322: Power of attorney from Alexander Sprunt to James Sprunt, 1876 (Box 13)
  - 7323: Bremen Office profit and loss statement, 1909 Jun. (Box 13)
  - 7326: Christmas lists, 1909-1914 (Box 13)
  - 7336: Aktien-Gesellschaft der Baltischen Baumwollspinnerei and Weberi-Reval, Estonia papers, 1930-1934 (Box 14)
  - 7346: Munds Brothers journal (daybook: Drugs), 1883 Oct.-1885 Apr. (Box 14)
  - 8000: Wilmington Compress and Warehouse Co. (Box 14)
    Not an original file. These records were found in Cashbook A. Balance sheets, 1880-1881 and 1885. Accounts of bales compressed, 1877-1878, and other accounts. Letter of 1885 about the firm's Tyler Press, built 1875.
- Pictures, undated
  The Pictures Series includes both photographs and illustrated pictures and advertisements. The majority of photographs are of the Alexander Sprunt and Son employees and facilities in Wilmington, N.C., and include the main office building on Front and Walnut Streets; office staff, including some photographs of the Sprunts; the Champion Compress and Warehouse facility; the S.S. Winston Salem (1920). The series also includes portraits and photographs of the Sprunt family both in Wilmington and abroad. Other images in the collection are: postcards and advertisements, as well as a set of photos by Cirkut Photos by Coovert in Memphis, Tennessee.
  - Pictures, undated (Box 14)
  - Pictures, undated (Box 15)
- Volumes, 1890s-1950s
  The company's nomenclature for some of the account books was not apparent, and it was necessary to substitute titles that it is hoped are approximately accurate, if not always precise. In addition, there was some difficulty in distinguishing between those volumes that belonged to the main office at Wilmington and those that belonged to other offices and subsidiaries. The company was a complex operation, and its accounting procedures changed over the years. Many volumes did not have labels.
  - Miscellaneous volumes
    - Audit reports, 1925 (Box 16)
      For period 1919-1923. Includes The Wilmington Corporation; the General Summary and Reconcilments; Walter P. Sprunt; William H. Sprunt; and Bremen Partnership.
    - Letterbooks, 1906-1908 (Box 17)
    - Code books and Stock Ledger, 1919-1948 (Box 18)
    - Minutes of Meetings of Stockholders and Board of Directors, 1919-1930 (Volume 1)
  - Ledgers
    The ledgers often contained records that are not necessarily part of a general ledger. These ledgers included such things as agent's ledgers, journals, account sales, consignments, claims, city cotton, check registers, cashbooks, trial balanaces, and others; some of which appear at other times as separate subsidiary account books. The inclusiveness of the ledgers is especially apparent during the late 1910s and 1920s.
    - Private Ledgers, 1907-1931 (Volume 2-7)
    - Ledger I, 1889-1890 (Volume 8)
    - Ledger I Index, undated (Volume 9)
    - Ledger J, 1890-1891 (Volume 9A)
    - Ledger K, 1891-1893 (Volume 10)
    - Ledger L, 1893-1895 (Volume 11)
    - Ledger M, 1895-1896 (Volume 12)
    - Ledger M Index, undated (Volume 13)
    - Ledger O, 1898-1901 (Volume 14)
    - Ledger, A-K, 1901-1905 (Volume 15)
    - Ledger, L-Z, 1901-1905 (Volume 16)
    - Ledger (includes some earlier accounts), 1905-1913 (Volume 16A)
    - Ledger, 1913-1914 (Volume 17, Volume 14)
    - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Volume 18)
    - Ledger, 1915-1916 (Volume 19)
    - Ledger, 1916-1917 (Volume 20)
    - Ledger, 1918 (Volume 21)
    - Ledger, 1919 Jan.-Jun. (Volume 22)
    - Ledger, 1919, Jun.-Dec. (Volume 23)
    - Ledger, 1920 (Volume 24)
    - Ledger, 1921 (Volume 25)
    - Ledger, 1922 (Volume 26)
    - Ledger, 1923 (Volume 27)
    - Ledger, 1924 (Volume 28)
    - Ledger, 1925 (Volume 29)
    - Ledger, 1926 (Volume 30)
    - Ledger, 1927, Jan.-May (Volume 31)
    - Ledger, 1927-1928 (Volume 32)
    - Ledger, 1928-1929 (Volume 33)
    - Ledger, 1929-1930 (Volume 34)
    - Ledger, 1930-1931 (Volume 35)
    - Ledger, 1931-1932 (Volume 36)
    - Ledger, 1932-1933 (Volume 37)
    - Ledger, 1933-1934 (Volume 38)
    - Ledger, 1934-1935 (Volume 39)
    - Ledger, 1935-1936 (Volume 40)
    - Ledger, 1936-1937 (Volume 41)
    - Ledger, 1937 Apr.-May (Volume 42)
    - Ledger, 1937-1938 (Volume 43)
    - Ledger, 1938-1939 (Volume 44)
    - Ledger, 1939-1940 (Volume 45)
    - Ledger, 1940-1941 (Volume 46)
    - Ledger, 1941-1942 (Volume 47)
    - Ledger, 1942-1943 (Volume 48)
    - Ledger, 1943-1944 (Volume 49)
    - Ledger, 1944-1945 (Volume 50)
    - Ledger, 1945-1946 (Volume 51)
    - Ledger, 1946-1947 (Volume 52)
    - Ledger, 1947-1948 (Volume 53)
    - Ledger, 1948-1952 (Volume 53, Volume 54)
    - Foreign Ledger, 1909-1910 (Volume 55)
    - Agents' Ledger, 1907-1909 (Volume 56)
    - Agents' Ledger, 1909-1911 (Volume 57)
    - Agents' Ledger, 1911-1912 (Volume 58)
    - Agents' Expenses, 1932-1933 (Volume 59)
  - Journals
    - Journal, 1878 Oct.-1883 Feb. (Volume 60)
    - Journal, 1883 Mar.-1885 Dec. (Volume 61)
    - Journal, 1891 Nov.-1893 Jan. (Volume 62)
    - Journal, 1893 Oct.-1895 Mar. (Volume 63)
    - Journal, 1894-1898 (Volume 64)
    - Journal, 1896 Nov.-1898 Oct. (Volume 65)
    - Journal, 1898 Sept.-1901 Dec. (Volume 66)
    - Journal, 1899 Oct.-1902 Oct. (Volume 67)
    - Journal, 1905 Mar.-Sept. (Volume 68)
    - Journal, 1905 July-1913 Aug. (Volume 69)
  - Cashbooks
    - Cashbook, 1884 Sept.-1888 Oct. (Volume 70)
    - Cashbook, 1888 Oct.-1891 Oct. (Volume 71)
    - Cashbook, 1891 Oct.-1894 Aug. (Volume 72)
    - Cashbook, 1896 May-1899 Oct. (Volume 73)
    - Cashbook, 1899 Oct.-1901 Oct. (Volume 74)
    - Cashbook, 1903 Dec.-1906 Dec. (Volume 72, Volume 75)
    - Cashbook, 1906 Dec.-1909 July (Volume 75, Volume 76)
    - Cashbook, 1909 Aug.-1910 Aug. (Volume 77)
    - Cash Journal, 1910 Sept.-1911 Aug. (Volume 78)
    - Cash Journal, 1911 Aug.-1912 Aug. (Volume 79)
    - Cash Journal, 1912 Aug.-1913 Aug. (Volume 80)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1919 (Volume 81)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1924-1925 Mar. (Volume 82)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1925 Apr.-Dec. (Volume 83)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1934 Jun.-1935 May (Volume 84)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1935 Jun.-1936 May (Volume 85)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1936 Jun.-1937 May (Volume 86)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1937 Jun.-1938 May (Volume 87)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1938 Jun.-1939 May (Volume 88)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1939 Jun.-1940 May (Volume 89)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1940 Jun.-1931 May (Volume 90)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1941 Jun.-1942 May (Volume 91)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1942 Jun.-1943 May (Volume 92)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1943 Jun.-1944 May (Volume 93)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1944 Jun.-1945 May (Volume 94)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1945 Jun.-1946 May (Volume 95)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1946 Jun.-1947 May (Volume 96)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1947 Jun.-1948 May (Volume 97)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1948 Jun.-1954 May (Volume 98)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1954 Jun.-1958 May (Volume 99)
    - Cash-Check-Journal Register, 1958 Jun.-1960 Jun. (Volume 100)
  - Purchases and Sales
    - Purchases Book, 1898 Sept.-1899 Aug. (Volume 101)
    - Purchases Book, 1906 Sept.-1907 May (Volume 102)
    - Purchases Book, 1911 Sept.-1912 Sept. (Volume 103)
    - Purchases and Sales Book, 1912 Sept.-1926 Dec. (Volume 104)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1925 Sept.-Dec. (Volume 105)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1926 Jan.-Jun. (Volume 106)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1926 Jun.-Dec. (Volume 107)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1927 Jan.-May (Volume 108)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1927 Jun.-1928 May (Volume 109)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1928 Jun.-1928 May (Volume 110)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1929 Jun.-1930 May (Volume 111)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1930 Jun.-1931 May (Volume 112)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1931 Jun.-1933 May (Volume 113)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1933 Jun.-1935 Nov. (Volume 114)
    - Purchases and Sales Journal, 1935 Nov.-1938 Mar. (Volume 115)
  - Cotton